Inventory of the Dorsey-Coupland Papers 1840-1876, 1843-1865
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Miscellaneous Items. (Box-folder 2:6-7)
  - Subscription list, 1860., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    List of subscriptions for building and organizing a Presbyterian Church in Williamsburg, Virginia.
  - List of female clerks, 1864., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    List of ladies appointed as clerks in Ordinance Bureau, Confederate States of America, Richmond, Virginia.
  - Card, June 1858., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Card of the "First Volunteer Regiment of Alabama, Admit Carter Coupland."
  - Card soliciting aid, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Card of the Ladies Southern Aid Association, soliciting aid in behalf of the family of Jefferson Davis.
  - Invitation to a social function, 9 February 1869., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Invitation to Captain and Mrs. J. H. Marshall to attend a social function of the Order of Myths.
  - Letter, n.d., 4 pages. 17 cm. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Daniel Murray... From a letter of the Hon. Francis S. Key, United States Attorney of the District of Columbia. Published by the American Tract Society.
  - Wedding Invitations, n.d., 5 items. (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Wedding invitations, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
      O.W. Brooke to Gussie M. McCoy.
    - Wedding invitations, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
      F.L. Glover to Mattie Stewart.
    - Wedding invitations, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
      John D. Freeland to Mary W. Goldthwaite.
    - Wedding invitations, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
      Leslie Marmaduke to Zemula Crawford.
    - Wedding invitations, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
      Charles O'Reilly to Alice M. Caulfield.
  - Memorandum, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Memorandum showing the arrangement of trees in an orchard.
  - Verse., 7 items. (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Advertising Card., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Advertising card with cut of Ford's Hotel, Richmond, Virginia.
  - Scrapbook, 1847-1853, n.d., 136 pages. 8 x 6.5 inches. (Box-folder 2:7)
    Scrapbook of Mrs. Juliana Dorsey and of Susan E. Henley Coupland [Mrs. John R. Coupland]. Note: The book contains newspaper clippings, a few of which are dated 1847-1853.